Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Basketball Negatives, circa 1926-1991; undated; 2
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 6
    - Kitching, Brent, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Item UA13020018-N-00617)
    - Kitching, Brent, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Item UA13020018-N-00618)
    - Kitching, Brent (with unidentified female in bookstore), 1965 Feb. (Box 4, Item UA13020018-N-00619)
    - Koffenberger, Ed (informal shots), 1947 (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04856)
    - Koffenberger, Ed (informal shots with unidentified males, note shot of a card game), 1947 (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04857)
    - Koffenberger, Ed, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04858)
    - Koffenberger, Ed, 1947 (Box 4, Item UA13020018-N-00620)
    - Koffenberger, Ed (receiving Adam Hat and Helm Award), 1947 May 6 (Box 4, Item UA13020018-N-00621)
    - Kolodziej, Tim, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00622)
    - Kolodziej, Tim, 1967 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00623)
    - Kramer, Pete, 1972 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00624)
    - Kubek, Bob (manager), 1941, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04859)
    - Kuhlmeier, Ray, 1967, 1968 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00625)
    - Kuhlmeier, Ray, 1969 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00626)
    - Kulpan, Jim, 1950 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00627)
    - Kunkle, Charlie, 1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04860)
    - Kunkle, Charlie, 1934-1935, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04861)
    - Lacy, Rudy, 1954 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00628)
    - Lakata, Bob, circa 1954-1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00629)
    - Lamley, Howard "Herky," 1954 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00630)
    - Larkin, Sid, 1943, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04862)
    - Latimer, Dick, 1951 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00631)
    - Lauteres, George, 1938, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04863)
    - Lee, Ronnie, 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00632)
    - Leister, Jack (Freshman team), 1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00633)
    - Leonard, Debbie, 1977 Apr. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00634)
    - Leopoldt, Dick (Freshman team), 1937, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04864)
    - Lewis, Cliff, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00635)
    - Lewis, Fred, circa 1930-1933, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04865)
    - Lewis, Jim (first African-American assistant coach), 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00636)
    - Lewis, Jim (first African-American assistant coach), 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00637)
    - Lewis, Jim (first African-American assistant coach), 1972 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00638)
    - Lewis, Jim (copy negative of a newspaper clipping), circa 1973-1974 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00639)
    - Lewis, Mike, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00640)
    - Lewis, Mike, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00641)
    - Lewis, Mike (with Bob Verga), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00642)
    - Lewis, Mike (with Coach Bubas), 1966, 1968 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00643)
    - Lewis, Mike, 1967 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00644)
    - Lewis, Mike (with Coach Bubas, color photos), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00645)
    - Lewis, Mike (informal shots on campus), 1968 Jan. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00646)
    - Liccardo, James (with William Ulrich, "New Jersey Boys"), 1963 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00647)
    - Liccardo, James, circa 1964-1965 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00648)
    - Liccardo, James, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00649)
    - Lind, Frederick, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00650)
    - Lind, Frederick, 1967, 1968 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00651)
    - Linney, Larry, 1979 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00652)
    - Linney, Larry, 1980 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00653)
    - Litz, Steve, 1968, 1969 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00654)
    - Litz, Steve, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00655)
    - Litz, Steve, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00656)
    - Loftis, Cedric, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04866)
    - Loftis, Cedric, 1942 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00657)
    - Loftis, Garland, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04867)
    - Loftis, Garland, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04868)
    - Loftis, Garland, 1947 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00658)
    - Loftis Brothers, 1942-1943, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04869)
    - Lohrey, Paul (manager, passport photo), 1983 Apr. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00659)
    - Lynch, Hal, 1949 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00660)
    - Mack, Connie, circa 1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04870)
    - Major, Howard, 1945-1946, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04871)
    - Mann, Ted, Jr., 1964 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00661)
    - Marco, Joe, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00662)
    - Marin, Jack, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00663)
    - Marin, Jack, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00664)
    - Marin, Jack (informal, in dorm room), circa 1964 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00665)
    - Marin, Jack (in suit and tie), 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00666)
    - Marin, Jack (copy negative of him playing for Chicago), undated (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00667)
    - Martin, Bill, 1947, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04872)
    - Martin, Bill, 1947 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00668)
    - Martin, Bill, circa 1948-1950 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00669)
    - Martin, John, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00670)
    - Mate, Kelly, 1943, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04873)
    - May, Reynolds, 1933-1934, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04874)
    - Mayer, Ronnie, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00671)
    - McBride, Elliott, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00672)
    - McCahan, Bill, 1941, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04875)
    - McCahan, Bill, 1942, Nitrate (Box 36, Item UA13020018-N-04876)
    - McGeachy, Neil, 1971, 1972 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00673)
    - McGrane, Art, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04877)
    - McKaig, Albert, 1964-1965, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00674)
    - McLeod, Phil, 1973 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00675)
    - McNeely, Doug, 1980 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00676)
    - McNeely, Doug, 1981 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00677)
    - McNeely, Doug, 1981 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00678)
    - McNeely, Doug (passport photo), 1983 Apr. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00679)
    - Melchionni, Gary, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00680)
    - Melchionni, Gary, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00681)
    - Melchionni, Gary, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00682)
    - Melchionni, Gary (copy negative of him playing for Phoenix), undated (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00683)
    - Metzler, Bob, 1947 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00684)
    - Mewhort, Buzz, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00685)
    - Mewhort, Buzz, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00686)
    - Miller, Alex, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04878)
    - Miller, Alex, 1947 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00687)
    - Miller, Don, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00688)
    - Miller, Ken (manager), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00689)
    - Minor, John, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04879)
    - Minor, John, 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04880)
    - Mock, Bill, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04881)
    - Morgan, Junior, circa 1955 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00690)
    - Morgan, Junior, circa 1955 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00691)
    - Morgan, Merrill, circa 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00692)
    - Morgan, Merrill, circa 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00693)
    - Morris, Johnny, circa 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00694)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1975 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00695)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1975 Oct. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00696)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1976 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00697)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1976 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00698)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1977 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00699)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1977 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00700)
    - Morrison, Harold, 1978 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00701)
    - Morrison, Harold (color), circa 1978 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00702)
    - Moses, George (passport photo), 1976 Apr. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00703)
    - Moses, George, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00704)
    - Moyer, Bill, 1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04882)
    - Moyer, Bill, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04883)
    - Moyer, Bill, 1938, 1941 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00705)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1959-1960 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00706)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1959-1960 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00707)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00708)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00709)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00710)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00711)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1961-1962 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00712)
    - Mullins, Jeff, circa 1961-1962 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00713)
    - Mullins, Jeff (color), circa 1962 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00714)
    - Mullins, Jeff (with Frank Harscher), 1963 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00715)
    - Mullins, Jeff (copy negative of him in San Francisco uniform), 1976 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00716)
    - Mullins, Jeff, 1976 Nov. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00717)
    - Murray, Terry, circa 1963-1964 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00718)
    - Murray, Terry, circa 1963-1964 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00719)
    - Naktenis, Pete, 1934-1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04884)
    - Neighborgall, Roger, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04885)
    - Newcome, Jim, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00720)
    - O'Mara, Bob, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04886)
    - O'Mara, Bob, 1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04887)
    - O'Connell, Dave, 1973, 1975 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00721)
    - O'Connor, Richie, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00722)
    - O'Connor, Richie, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00723)
    - Parker, Clarence "Ace," 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04888)
    - Parsons, Bill (Freshman team), 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04889)
    - Parsons, Bill, 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04890)
    - Parsons, Bill, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00724)
    - Pergram, Bernard, 1949 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00725)
    - Peters, Tommy, 1953 (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04891)
    - Podger, Ken, 1934-1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04892)
    - Podger, Ken, 1937-1938, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04893)
    - Polack, Ernest "Budd," "Bunt," circa 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04894)
    - Pope, Bucky, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00726)
    - Posen, John, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00727)
    - Price, Glenn, 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04895)
    - Price, Glenn, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00728)
    - Price, Glenn, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04896)
    - Price, Glenn, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04897)
    - Price, Glenn (with Cyril Valascek), 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04898)
    - Raksnis, Charlie, 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00729)
    - Rankin, Bob, 1959 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00730)
    - Rappaport, Ken (Freshman team), 1954 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00731)
    - Rauch, Marshall, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04899)
    - Redding, Chris, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00732)
    - Redding, Chris, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00733)
    - Redding, Chris, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00734)
    - Redding, Chris, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00735)
    - Redding, Chris, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00736)
    - Redding, Chris, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00737)
    - Reiber, Bill (Freshman team), 1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00738)
    - Riedy, Bob, 1966 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00739)
    - Riedy, Bob (informal, on-campus), 1965 Jan. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00740)
    - Riedy, Bob (with Larry Miller), 1965 Jan. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00741)
    - Riegel, Bill, 1953 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00742)
    - Righter, Ron, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00743)
    - Righter, Ron, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00744)
    - Riley, Joe, 1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04900)
    - Riley, Joe, 1936, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04901)
    - Riley, Joe, 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04902)
    - Robertson, Jerry, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00745)
    - Roellke, Bob, 1945-1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04903)
    - Rogers, George, circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04904)
    - Rogers, Jim, 1955 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00746)
    - Rosenthal, Richard, 1956 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-04905)
    - Rothbaum, Sammy, 1941-1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04906)
    - Salisbury, Steve, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00747)
    - Sands, Sandy (manager), 1964 Oct. (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00748)
    - Sapp, Bill, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00749)
    - Sapp, Carl, 1947, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04907)
    - Sapp, Carl, 1949, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04908)
    - Sapp, Carl, 1949 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00750)
    - Saunders, Larry, 1969 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00751)
    - Saunders, Larry (with Coach Bucky Waters), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00752)
    - Saunders, Larry, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00753)
    - Saunders, Larry, 1970 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00754)
    - Saunders, Larry, 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00755)
    - Scales, John, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00756)
    - Scarborough, Dave, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00757)
    - Schalow, Jack (Assistant Coach), 1971 (Box 5, Item UA13020018-N-00758)
    - Schmidt, Fred, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00759)
    - Schmidt, Fred, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00760)
    - Schmidt, Fred, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00761)
    - Schmidt, Fred, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00762)
    - Schmidt, Paul, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00763)
    - Seward, John "Bubber," 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04909)
    - Seward, John "Bubber," 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04910)
    - Seward, John "Bubber" (informal), 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04911)
    - Seward, John "Bubber" (informal), 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04912)
    - Seward, John "Bubber," 1942 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00764)
    - Shabel, Fred, 1954 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00765)
    - Shabel, Fred, 1957 Sept. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00766)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1970 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00767)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1970 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00768)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00769)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00770)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00771)
    - Shaw, Alan, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00772)
    - Shaw, John, circa 1930-1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04913)
    - Shokes, Edward, 1937 (Freshman team), Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04914)
    - Shokes, Edward, 1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04915)
    - Shokes, Edward, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04916)
    - Simmons, Buck, 1949 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00773)
    - Sims, Don, 1954 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00774)
    - Skibstead, Wesley, 1947 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00775)
    - Smiley, Glen, 1967, 1968 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00776)
    - Smiley, Glen, 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00777)
    - Smiley, Glen (with Coach Bucky Waters), 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00778)
    - Smith, Bruce (manager), 1971 Feb. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00779)
    - Smith, Jack (Freshman team), 1956 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00780)
    - Soloman, Ray (Freshman team), 1956 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00781)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1975 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00782)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1976 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00783)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1976 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00784)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1976 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00785)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1977 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00786)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1977 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00787)
    - Spanarkel, Jim (color), circa 1977 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00788)
    - Spanarkel, Jim, 1978 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00789)
    - Spanarkel, Jim (copy negative of him playing for Dallas), undated (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00790)
    - Spuhler, Ray "Hap," 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04917)
    - Stark, Bill, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04918)
    - Steinwedel, Steve (Assistant Coach), 1978 Oct. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00791)
    - Stephenson, Bob, circa 1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00792)
    - Stewart, Bob, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00793)
    - Stott, Grady, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04919)
    - Straten, Roland, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00794)
    - Strauss, Bob, 1951 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00795)
    - Suddath, Jim, 1977 Nov. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00796)
    - Suddath, Jim, circa 1977, 1978 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00797)
    - Suddath, Jim, 1979 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00798)
    - Suddath, Jim (India trip, copy of color slides), 1979 Oct. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00799)
    - Suddath, Jim, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00800)
    - Suk, Bill, 1973 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00801)
    - Swindell, Ed, 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04920)
    - Taylor, Vince, 1978 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00802)
    - Taylor, Vince, 1979 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00803)
    - Taylor, Vince, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00804)
    - Taylor, Vince, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00805)
    - Taylor, Vince, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00806)
    - Teer, Tim, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00807)
    - Thomas, James C., 1937-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04921)
    - Thomas, Susan (secretary), 1979 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00808)
    - Thomas, Zach, circa 1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00809)
    - Thompson, Herb, circa 1931-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04922)
    - Thompson, Jim, circa 1931-1932, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04923)
    - Thorne, Bob, circa 1928-1930, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04924)
    - Thuemmel, Bob, 1955 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00810)
    - Tison, Hack, 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00811)
    - Tison, Hack, 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00812)
    - Tison, Hack, 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00813)
    - Tison, Hack, 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00814)
    - Tison, Hack (informal), 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00815)
    - Tison, Hack (informal), 1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00816)
    - Tissaw, Mike (informal), 1979 Sept. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00817)
    - Tissaw, Mike, 1979 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00818)
    - Tissaw, Mike, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00819)
    - Tissaw, Mike, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00820)
    - Tissaw, Mike, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00821)
    - Tobin, Don, 1954 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00822)
    - Turner, Hal, 1954 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00823)
    - Ulrich, Bill, circa 1963-1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00824)
    - Ulrich, Bill, circa 1963-1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00825)
    - Ulrich, Bill, circa 1963-1964 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00826)
    - Ulrich, Bill (with Coach Bucky Waters - signing), undated (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00827)
    - Vacendak, Steve, circa 1964-1965 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00828)
    - Vacendak, Steve (informal), 1965-1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00829)
    - Vacendak, Steve (in suit and tie), 1966 Nov. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00830)
    - Valasek, Cyril (Cy) (Freshman team), 1937, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04925)
    - Valasek, Cyril (Cy), 1938-1939, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04926)
    - Valasek, Cyril (Cy), 1938-1939 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00831)
    - Valasek, Cyril (Cy), 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04927)
    - Vandenberg, Steve, 1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00832)
    - Vandenberg, Steve, 1967, 1968 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00833)
    - Van Schoik, Dick, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00834)
    - Vehe, Bob, 1942, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04928)
    - Verga, Bob (informal), 1964 Dec. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00835)
    - Verga, Bob, 1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00836)
    - Verga, Bob (in suit and tie), 1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00837)
    - Verga, Bob (with Coach Bubas), 1966, 1967 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00838)
    - Verga, Bob (with Coach Bubas, color photo), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00839)
    - Vernon, Bob, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00840)
    - Vick, Paul (manager), 1965 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00841)
    - Wallingford, Tom, 1947, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04929)
    - Wallingford, Tom, 1947 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00842)
    - Warren, Richard, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00843)
    - Warwick, Robert "Shank," circa 1929-1931, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04930)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach), 1965 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00844)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach) (color), circa 1966 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00845)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach), circa 1966-1968 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00846)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach), 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00847)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach), 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00848)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach) (after 100th victory), 1971 Feb. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00849)
    - Waters, Bucky (Head Coach), 1972 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00850)
    - Watson, Bill, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00851)
    - Wayand, Bill, circa 1958 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00852)
    - Weaver, Phil, circa 1931-1934, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04931)
    - Wendelin, Ron, 1966, 1967 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00853)
    - Wendelin, Ron (with Dave Golden, color), 1966-1967 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00854)
    - Wendt, Greg, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00855)
    - Wendt, Greg, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00856)
    - Wentz, Earle, 1934-1935, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04932)
    - Wenzel, Bob (Assistant Coach), 1974 Aug. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00857)
    - Wenzel, Bob (Assistant Coach), 1978 Oct. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00858)
    - West, Robby, 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00859)
    - West, Robby (with Coach Bucky Waters), 1969 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00860)
    - West, Robby, 1970 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00861)
    - West, Robby, 1970 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00862)
    - West, Robby, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00863)
    - West, Robby, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00864)
    - West, Robby, 1971 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00865)
    - Wetmore, Bill, 1941, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04933)
    - Whiting, Dick, 1945-1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04934)
    - Whitted, Gordon, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00866)
    - Whitted, Gordon, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00867)
    - Whitten, Ward, 1945-1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04935)
    - Williams, Allen, 1979 Sept. (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00868)
    - Williams, Allen, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00869)
    - Williams, Allen, 1980 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00870)
    - Williams, Allen, 1981 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00871)
    - Williams, Tom, 1945-1946, Nitrate (Box 37, Item UA13020018-N-04936)
    - Wilmer, Bill (manager), 1976 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00872)
    - Williamson, Scott, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00873)
    - Williamson, Scott, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00874)
    - Williamson, Scott, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00875)
    - Williamson, Scott, circa 1961 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00876)
    - Wilson, Charlie "Stick," 1959-1960 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00877)
    - Winkin, John, 1941 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00878)
    - Wittner, Dale, 1959 (Box 6, Item UA13020018-N-00879)